Is the Wall as big
as they say?
Bigger.
- How much longer?
- A few more days.
I found something
at the Fist of the First Men.
What does it do?
I'm not sure
that it does anything.
You're not supposed
to be here.
- If your father knew--
- He said you're a traitor.
I am. child.
You must get bored
down here.
I brought you
something to read.
My lady. I can't
read the words.
I wouldn't know
where to start.
At the beginning.
This word is Aegon.
The Yunkish train
bed slaves. not soldiers.
- We can defeat them.
- But they won't meet us on the field.
They have strong walls.
Women in our position
must make the best
of our circumstances.
How do I make the best
of my circumstances?
I have to marry him.
I didn't ask
for this marriage.
I will marry Sansa Stark
and do my duty by her.
My feelings for you
have not changed.
Listen to me.
my lady.
I'm not your lady.
I'm your whore.
You will release
every slave in Yunkai.
You are mad.
We have powerful friends.
Friends who would take great
pleasure in destroying you.
Perhaps we'll make
a slave of you as well.
He said he had
powerful friends.
Who was he talking about?
- I don't know.
- Find out.
Haven't you ever wondered
where your strength came from?
- Your blood is noble.
- I'm just a bastard.
The bastard of Robert
of the House Baratheon.
There is power
in a king's blood.
You're a liar!
You lied to Gendry.
you lied to me.
Now--
- Anguy. bring her back.
- Come back. girl!
Kick all you like.
wolf girl.
Won't do you no good.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ Game of Thrones 3x08 ♪
Second Sons
Original Air Date on May 19. 2013
== sync. corrected by elderman ==
I'll give you one try. girl.
Kill me and you're free.
But if I live.
I'll break both your hands.
Go on. hit me.
Hit me hard.
Sulk all you want.
The truth is.
you're lucky.
You don't want to be
alone out here. girl.
Someone worse than me
would find you.
There's no one
worse than you.
Ha. you never knew
my brother.
He once killed a man
for snoring.
There's plenty
worse than me.
There's men who like
to beat little girls.
men who like
to rape them.
I saved your sister
from some of them.
You're lying.
Ask her. if you
ever see her again.
Ask her who
came back for her
when the mob
had her on her back.
They would have
taken her every which way
and left her there
with her throat cut open.
Is that the Blackwater?
The Blackwater?
Where do you think
I'm taking you?
Back to King's Landing
to Joffrey and the queen.
Fuck Joffrey.
Fuck the queen.
That's the Red Fork.
I'm taking you
to the Twins.
But why?
Because your mother
and brother will be there
and they'll pay me for you.
Why would they be
at the Twins?
Those outlaws you love
so much never told you?
The whole countryside
is yapping about it.
Your uncle is marrying
one of the Frey girls.
So quit trying
to bash my skull in
and we might just make it there
in time for the wedding.
Men who fight for gold
have neither honor nor loyalty.
They cannot be trusted.
They can be trusted to kill
you if they're well paid.
The Yunkish
are paying them well.
You know these men?
Only by the broken swords
on their banners.
They're called
the Second Sons.
A company led by
a Braavosi named Mero.
"The Titan's Bastard."
Is he more titan
or bastard?
He's a dangerous man.
khaleesi.
They all are.
How many?
2.000. Your Grace.
Armored and mounted.
Enough to make
a difference?
It's hard to collect
wages from a corpse.
I'm sure the sellswords
prefer to fight for the winning side.
I imagine you're right.
I'd like to talk to the
Titan's Bastard about winning.
He may not agree
to meet.
He will.
A man who fights for gold can't
afford to lose to a girl.
Your Grace.
allow me to present
the captains
of the Second Sons--
Mero of Braavos.
Prendahl na Ghezn.
and...
Daario Naharis.
You are the Mother
of Dragons?
I swear I fucked you once
in a pleasure house in Lys.
- Mind your tongue.
- Why?
I didn't mind hers.
She licked my ass
like she was born to do it.
You. slave girl.
bring wine.
We have no slaves here.
You'll all be slaves
after the battle
unless I save you.
Take your clothes off
and come and sit on Mero's lap
and I may give you
my Second Sons.
Give me your Second Sons
and I may not have you gelded.
Ser Barristan. how many men
fight for the Second Sons?
Under 2.000. Your Grace.
We have more.
don't we?
10.000 Unsullied.
I'm only a young girl.
new to the ways of war.
but perhaps a seasoned
captain like yourself
can explain to me
how you propose to defeat us.
I hope the old man is better with
a sword than he is with a lie.
You have 8.000 Unsullied.
You're very young
to be a captain.
He's not a captain.
He's a lieutenant.
Even if your numbers
are right.
you must admit the odds
don't favor your side.
The Second Sons have faced
worse odds and won.
The Second Sons have
faced worse odds and run.
Or you could
fight for me.
We've taken
the slavers' gold.
We fight for Yunkai.
I would pay
you as much and more.
Our contract
is our bond.
If we break our bond.
no one will hire
the Second Sons again.
Ride with me and you'll
never need another contract.
You'll have gold and castles
and lordships of your choosing
when I take back
the Seven Kingdoms.
You have no ships.
You have no siege weapons.
You have no cavalry.
A fortnight ago.
I had no army.
A year ago.
I had no dragons.
You have two days
to decide.
Show me your cunt. I want
to see if it's worth fighting for.
You seem to be
enjoying my wine.
Perhaps you'd like
a flagon to help you ponder.
Only a flagon?
And what are my brothers
in arms to drink?
- A barrel. then.
- Good.
The Titan's Bastard
does not drink alone.
In the Second Sons.
we share everything.
After the battle.
maybe we'll all share you.
I'll come looking for you
when this is over.
Ser Barristan.
if it comes to battle.
kill that one first.
Gladly. Your Grace.
Half Robert.
half lowborn.
Show the boy
to his chambers.
Have the maids draw him
a bath and find him some decent clothes.
I'll come visit you soon.
What do you mean
to do with him?
You know what I mean
to do with him.
Then why bathe him
and dress him in fine clothes?
If it needs to be done. do it.
Don't torture the boy.
Have you ever slaughtered
a lamb. my king?
No.
If the lamb
sees the knife.
she panics.
Her panic seeps
into her meat.
darkens it.
fouls the flavor.
You've slaughtered
many lambs?
And none have seen
the blade.
"And tho-- and thowg...
V-v-visenya...
Targaryen...
rod-- rode
Vhagar--
Vhag--"
Fuck me.
"Visenya Targaryen
rode Vhagar.
the smallest
of the dragons.
though still...
large enog--
enough-- enough
to swallow
a horse whole."
Your Grace.
They feeding you enough?
Two meals a day.
Cold for breakfast.
hot for supper.
I cannot complain.
You don't belong
in a place like this.
Well. it's sad to say.
but I've seen worse.
Yeah.
I'm sorry about your son.
Didn't get the chance
to tell you before.
Good lad.
Loyal lad.
Melisandre's returned.
I didn't know
she'd been gone.
Came back
with a bastard boy.
Robert's bastard boy.
Why?
She says there's power
in king's blood.
She's going to kill him.
Sacrifice him.
Forgive me. Your Grace.
I'm not a learned man.
but is there a difference
between kill and sacrifice?
The boy is your nephew.
What of it?
We're at war.
Why should I spare the son
of some tavern slut
Robert bedded
one drunken night?
Because he has
your blood in his veins.
So did Renly.
Renly wronged you.
Renly declared himself king when
the throne belonged to you.
He raised an army.
stole your bannermen.
This boy has
done you no harm.
- He's an innocent.
- How many boys live in Westeros?
How many girls?
How many men? How many women?
The darkness will devour
them all. she says.
The night that never ends.
Unless I triumph.
I never asked for this.
No more than I asked
to be king.
We do not choose
our destiny.
but we must do
our duty. no?
Great or small.
we must do our duty.
What's one bastard boy
against a kingdom?
Your Grace.
why did you come
to see me today?
I came to free you.
If you swear never to raise your
hand to the Lady Melisandre again.
I swear it.
I can't swear never
to speak against her.
You have little regard
for your own life.
Quite little. Your Grace.
Verging on none.
You could have freed me
yesterday or tomorrow.
but you came to me now
before this boy is put to the knife
because you knew
I'd counsel restraint.
You came to hear me say it
because you believe it yourself.
You're not a man
who slaughters innocents
for gain or glory.
When my son was five
he said to me.
"I don't ever
want to die."
I wanted to say to him.
"You won't. child. You won't ever."
I hated the idea of him
lying awake in the dark. afraid.
I think mothers and fathers
made up the gods
because they wanted their children
to sleep through the night.
I saw a vision
in the flames.
A great battle
in the snow.
I saw it.
And you saw whatever
she gave birth to.
I never believed.
but when you see the truth.
when it's right there
in front of you
as real as these iron bars.
how can you deny
her god is real?
Little dragon bitch.
She talks too much.
You talk too much.
She won't talk so much
when she's choking on my cock.
8.000 Unsullied stand
between her and your cock.
My cock will find a way.
Tell him.
Is there any place
that my cock can't reach?
She'll tell me whatever
you pay her to tell me.
Daario Naharis. the whore
who doesn't like whores.
I like them very much.
I just refuse to pay them.
And I'm no whore.
my friend.
She sells her sheath
and you sell your blade.
- What's the difference?
- I fight for beauty.
For beauty?
We fight for gold.
The gods gave men two gifts to
entertain ourselves before we die--
the thrill of fucking a woman
who wants to be fucked
and the thrill of killing
a man who wants to kill you.
You'll die young.
What do we do
about the dragon girl?
We can't beat 8.000 Unsullied
on the battlefield.
There won't be a battle. And we don't
have to deal with her eunuchs.
We only have
to deal with her.
- She's well guarded.
- Tonight's a new moon.
One of us slips into her camp past
her Unsullied and her knights.
Which one of us?
Close your eyes. love.
Three coins.
A coin from Meereen.
a coin from Volantis.
and a coin from Braavos.
The Braavosi
does the deed.
One for each
of us. darling.
No peeking.
Do you hear me?
Follow my voice.
I'm right here.
You have
something for me?
Valar morghulis.
Lady Sansa.
You look very handsome.
my lord.
Oh. yes.
The husband
of your dreams.
But you do
look glorious.
Perhaps we could have
a moment alone.
Do you mind?
Podrick. could you escort
Lady Stark's handmaiden?
My lady.
I want you to know
I didn't ask for this.
I hope I will not
disappoint you. my lord.
No. don't.
You don't have to speak to me
as a prisoner anymore.
You won't be a prisoner
after today.
You'll be my wife.
I suppose that's a different
kind of prison.
I just wanted to say--
I'm just trying
to say very badly--
I just--
just want to say
I know how you feel.
I doubt that
very much. my lord.
You're right.
I have no idea
how you feel.
And you have no idea
how I feel.
But I promise you
one thing. my lady.
I won't ever hurt you.
Do you drink wine?
When I have to.
Well. today you have to.
You look radiant.
Your Grace.
Radiant?
Why radiant?
It's the word
that came to mind.
We're going
to be sisters soon.
We should be friends.
You're a musical girl.
aren't you?
I imagine you have
a lovely voice.
A better dancer
than a singer. I'm afraid.
Ah. but you know the song
"The Rains of Castamere"?
Of course. They play it
so often here at court.
So you know the story
of House Reyne of Castamere?
Not as well as you.
I'm sure.
House Reyne
was a powerful family.
Very wealthy.
The second wealthiest
in Westeros.
Aren't the Tyrells the second
wealthiest family in Westeros now?
Of course. ambitious climbers
don't want to stop
on the second highest rung.
If only you could take
that final step.
you'd see further
than all the rest.
You'd be alone with nothing
but blue sky above you.
So Lord Reyne
built a castle
as grand as Casterly Rock.
He gave his wife diamonds
larger than any
my mother ever wore.
And finally one day.
he rebelled
against my father.
Do you know where
House Reyne is now?
Gone.
A gentle word.
Why not say slaughtered?
Every man. woman.
and child
put to the sword.
I remember seeing
their bodies hanging
high above the gates
of Casterly Rock.
My father let them rot
up there all summer.
It was a long summer.
"And now the rains
weep o'er their halls.
and not a soul to hear."
If you ever
call me sister again.
I'll have you strangled
in your sleep.
What are you doing?
Your father's gone.
As the father
of the realm.
it is my duty to give you away
to your husband.
You may now
cloak the bride
and bring her
under your protection.
Could you...
Thank you.
Your Grace.
my lords. my ladies.
we stand here in the sight
of gods and men
to witness the union
of man and wife.
One flesh. one heart.
one soul.
now and forever.
Have you ever
seen one like it?
I've never seen anything
like any of this.
Not in my life.
It's shocking. isn't it.
the first time
you encounter real wealth?
When I was your age.
I lived on one bowl of stew a day.
And stew
is a kind word for it.
In Flea Bottom we called them
bowls of brown.
We'd pretend that the meat
in them was chicken.
We knew
it wasn't chicken.
Here. taste this.
You think I'm trying
to poison you?
That's good.
That's really good.
Where do you think
it's from?
I couldn't even guess.
Doesn't matter. does it?
It's the real thing
or it's not.
You only need a tongue
to tell the difference.
Go on.
have some more.
You still
don't trust it.
You think this
is all a mistake
and that you'll have to pay
somehow for every bite you take.
That thought had
crossed my mind. yeah.
There are no mistakes.
Not for us.
I'm a mistake.
I'm only here because
my father grabbed my mother
instead of the girl
next to her in the tavern.
Your father chose your mother because
the Lord of Light willed it.
He willed it so you
could be here right now
with a power inside you
you can't even begin
to understand.
And He brought me here
to draw it from you
and birth it
into the world.
We're both a part
of His plan.
He wants this for us.
No. He demands
this of us.
I don't understand.
This--
this doesn't seem
very religious.
According to whom?
The Silent Sisters?
With their stern looks.
muzzled mouths.
and dried-up cunts?
What have their gods
done for you?
Hmm?
When you pray to them.
what's their answer?
A god is real
or he's not.
You only need eyes
to see.
Death is coming
for everyone and everything.
A darkness that will
swallow the dawn.
And we can stop it.
you and I.
Let me show you
what you have inside you.
Come fight death with me.
What are you doing?
You have to trust me.
What--?
Get it away.
Get it off me.
Don't fight. don't fight.
They won't take much.
Why are you
doing this?
I told you there's power
in the blood of kings.
And you have so much blood.
No. No. no. no. no!
Not there.
Not there!
You can blame Ser Davos.
He didn't believe in
the power of king's blood.
He wanted a demonstration.
Please.
Please. Your Grace.
My lord!
The usurper Robb Stark.
The usurper Balon Greyjoy.
The usurper
Joffrey Baratheon.
So their son
will be your nephew.
After you're wed
to Cersei. of course.
And you will be
the king's stepfather
and brother-in-law.
When you marry the king.
Joffrey's mother will
become his sister-in-law
and your son
will be Loras' nephew?
Grandson?
I'm not sure.
But your brother will become
your father-in-law.
That much
is beyond dispute.
Will you pardon me.
my lord?
Of course. Of course.
En-- enjoy.
Perhaps you could talk
to your bride-to-be instead.
I've got a lifetime for that.
Stay.
You seem rather drunk.
Rather less
than I plan to be.
Isn't it a man's duty to be
drunk at his own wedding?
This isn't about
your wedding.
Renly Baratheon
had a wedding.
Your wife needs a child.
a Lannister child.
as soon as possible.
- And?
- If you're going to give her one.
you need to perform.
What did you once call me?
A drunken little
lust-filled beast.
- More than once.
- There you have it.
Nothing to worry about.
Drinking and lust.
no man can match me
in these things.
I am the god
of tits and wine.
I shall build
a shrine to myself
at the next brothel
I visit.
You can drink.
you can joke.
you can engage
in juvenile attempts
to make your father
uncomfortable.
but you will do your duty.
Well...
My father once told me--
Nobody cares what
your father once told you.
Congratulations.
my lady.
Thank you.
Your Grace.
Well. you've done it.
You've married a Lannister.
Soon you'll have
a Lannister baby.
It's a dream come true
for you. isn't it?
What a glorious day.
Yes. Your Grace.
I suppose it doesn't
really matter
which Lannister
puts the baby into you.
Maybe I'll pay you
a visit tonight
after my uncle
passes out.
How'd you like that?
You wouldn't?
That's all right. Ser Meryn and
Ser Boros will hold you down.
Time for the bedding
ceremony.
There will be
no bedding ceremony.
Where's your respect
for tradition. Uncle?
Come. everyone.
Pick her up and carry her
to her wedding bed.
Get rid of her gown. She won't
be needing it any longer.
Ladies. attend to my uncle.
He's not heavy.
There will be
no bedding ceremony.
if I command it.
Then you'll be fucking
your own bride
with a wooden cock.
What did you say?
What did you say?!
I believe we can dispense
with the bedding. Your Grace.
I'm sure Tyrion did not mean
to threaten the king.
A bad joke. Your Grace.
Made out of envy
of your own royal manhood.
Mine is so small.
My poor wife won't
even know I'm there.
Your uncle is clearly
quite drunk. Your Grace.
I am.
Guilty.
But--
but it is my wedding night.
My tiny drunk cock
and I have a job to do.
Come. wife.
I vomited on a girl once
in the middle of the act.
Not proud of it.
But I think honesty
is important
between a man and wife.
don't you agree?
Come. I'll tell you
all about it.
Put you in the mood.
Is that wise.
my lord?
Tyrion. Sansa.
My name is Tyrion.
Is that wise. Tyrion?
Nothing was ever wiser.
Astoundingly long.
What?
Neck.
You have one.
How old are you exactly?
14.
Well. talk won't
make you any older.
My lord father
has commanded me
to consummate this marriage.
Stop.
I can't.
I could. I won't.
But your father--
If my father wants
someone to get fucked.
I know where he can start.
I won't share your bed.
Not until you want me to.
What if I never
want you to?
And so my watch begins.
19?
Yes. Your Grace.
How can anyone
speak 19 languages?
It only took Your Grace a year to
learn Dothraki reasonably well.
Yes. well. it was
either learn Dothraki
or grunt at my husband
and hope--
what do you mean
reasonably well?
Dothraki is difficult
for the mouth to master.
So guttural and harsh.
Athjahakar.
Athjahaka.
Ath-ja-hakar.
Athjahakar.
Well. I suppose
I'm a bit out of practice.
Your High Valyrian
is very good. Your Grace.
The gods could not devise
a more perfect tongue.
It is the only proper
language for poetry.
No screaming or she dies.
What do you want?
You.
Let her go.
Don't scream.
lovely girl.
You were sent here
to kill me?
So why haven't you?
I don't want to.
What do your captains
have to say about that?
You should ask them.
Why?
We had philosophical
differences.
- Over what?
- Your beauty.
It meant more to me
than it did to them.
You're a strange man.
I'm the simplest man
you'll ever meet.
I only do
what I want to do.
And this is supposed
to impress me?
Yes.
Why would I trust a man
who murders his comrades?
They ordered me
to murder you.
I told them
I preferred not to.
They told me
I had no choice.
I told them
I am Daario Naharis.
I always have a choice.
They drew their swords
and I drew mine.
Will you fight for me?
Swear to me.
The Second Sons are yours
and so is Daario Naharis.
My sword is yours.
my life is yours.
my heart is yours.
You really
ought to knock.
I brought your breakfast.
It's getting dark.
We could stay here
for the night.
How hard can it be
to build a fire?
It doesn't matter.
Come under the furs.
We can keep each other warm.
He winked at me before.
- I doubt it.
- I saw him wink at me.
He blinked.
I suppose it's a rather
philosophical difference
between a wink
and a blink.
A what?
Well. I mean.
there's no real difference.
A wink is on purpose.
You thought of a name yet?
It would be easier to refer
to him if he had a name.
Sometimes do you talk fancy
on purpose to confuse me?
What? No.
This is just
the way I talk.
I'll build that fire.
Don't you think
he should have a name?
I don't know
many boys' names.
Let's see.
there's Duncan.
Kevan. Jon...
Guymon.
Feldan.
Tristifer.
Craster.
Uh. yes.
Maybe that's not--
Mormont.
That's a lovely idea.
but Mormont's a last name.
Why is it a last name?
Well. it's a family name.
For instance.
I'm Samwell Tarly.
Samwell is my birth name
and Tarly
is my family name.
You see?
So my father is also a Tarly.
His name
is Samwell Tarly. too?
No. Randyll Tarly.
Randyll is a handsome name.
Please don't
name him Randyll.
Is your father
cruel like mine?
Different manner of cruel.
Not Randyll. then.
Don't.
Don't go out there.
I'll be back.
I just want to look.
Go inside.
Go back inside.
I'll--
It's come for the baby.
Stay back!
You stay back!
No. you can't
have him! No!
No!
Sync by Ahuruglica
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org